var salts_acids = [
    {
        question: "Metal + water -> ?",
        answers: {
            a: "metal hydroxide + hydrogen",
            b: "metal oxide + hydrogen",
            c: "metal hydroxide + water",
            d: "metal sulfate + water"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Metal + acid -> ?",
        answers: {
            a: "salt + water",
            b: "salt + hydrogen",
            c: "salt",
            d: "metal oxide + water"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Nitric acid forms which type of salt with metals?",
        answers: {
            a: "Metal sulfate",
            b: "Metal hydronitrate",
            c: "Metal nitrate",
            d: "Metal nitride"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What colour flame does potassium produce in water?",
        answers: {
            a: "Green",
            b: "Lilac",
            c: "Yellow",
            d: "Blue"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Acid + ammonia -> ?",
        answers: {
            a: "ammonium salt + water",
            b: "ammonium salt",
            c: "salt + hydrogen",
            d: "ammonium salt + carbon dioxide"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What must NOT be done when preparing a sample of salt?",
        answers: {
            a: "heat the acid",
            b: "add the metal/metal compound with stirring",
            c: "evaporate the excess water",
            d: "boil the acid"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    }
]

var organisation = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a level of organisation?",
        answers: {
            a: "DNA",
            b: "The heart",
            c: "Tissues",
            d: "Organ systems"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is the correct order of organisation, from largest to smallest?",
        answers: {
            a: "Cells, DNA, Organs, Organ systems, Tissues, Organisms",
            b: "DNA, Cells, Organs, Tissues, Organ systems, Organisms",
            c: "DNA, Cells, Tissues, Organs, Organ systems, Organisms",
            d: "DNA, Tissues, Cells, Organs, Organ systems, Organisms"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is an example of an organ?",
        answers: {
            a: "The liver",
            b: "Muscles",
            c: "The gut",
            d: "The endocrine system"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these statements is false?",
        answers: {
            a: "The heart is an organ.",
            b: "Tissues are groups of cells.",
            c: "Not all cells contain DNA.",
            d: "Organs contain tissues with a similar purpose."
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Give the correct definition for a cell.",
        answers: {
            a: "A group of tissues working together.",
            b: "The building blocks of living organisms, which perform important functions.",
            c: "A living thing containing several organ systems.",
            d: "An organ system which contains the heart."
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    }
]